

Val-de-Marne, France. +33 6 10 76 79 48 sambell912@gmail.com

Theoretical biophysicist specialised in stochastic systems and critical phenomena. Strong ability to translate problems into mathematical models, investigate these models, and communicate the results to a wider audience.

## **SKILLS**

## **EXPERIENCE**

Post-doctoral researcher,

Jun 2019-Present

Institut Curie, Paris, France.

Working on models of active matter and critical phenomena, specifically for the influence of external fields on epithelial monolayers.

Let's try another paragraph and see if this one works or not.

**PhD, Activation problems in biology**, Oct 2015–Jun 2019 Cavendish Laboratory, University of Cambridge, UK.

Published 8 research papers What else did I do?

## **LANGUAGES**

**English** Native speaker

French B2/C1

**Spanish** Semi-professional

proficiency

**EDUCATION** 

MSci, Experimental & Theoretical Physics,

Oct 2014–Jun 2015

Trinity College, University of Cambridge, UK.

BA, Natural Sciences (ETP),

Oct 2011-Jun 2014

Trinity College, University of Cambridge, UK.